压制:随Feng
Royals
歌手 Lorde
I've never seen a diamond in the flesh
我从未见过璀璨的钻石
I cut my teeth on wedding rings in the movies
只用过电影里的婚戒来拔牙
And I'm not proud of my address
我住的也不是富人区
In the torn up town
住在一个破败的小镇上
No post code envy
不会让人眼红
But every song's like gold teeth
每首歌都庸俗如镶着黄金牙
Grey goose, trippin' in the bathroom
喝着伏特加 在自家打理形象
Blood stains, ball gowns, trashin' the hotel room
血腥 狂欢 在酒店搞破坏
We don't care, we're driving cadillacs in our dreams
对此我们习以为常 梦里的凯迪拉克毕竟遥远
But everybody's like cristal, maybach
但每个人都喜欢水晶 迈巴赫
Diamonds on your time piece
手表镶满钻石
Jet planes, islands, tigers on a gold leash
乘着飞机去小岛用金链子套老虎玩的生活
We don't care, we aren't caught up in your love affair
我们不在乎这些 我对你的富贵梦廖无兴趣
And we'll never be royals..
我们无法成为贵族
It don't run in our blood
没有那么高贵的血统
That kind of lux just ain't for us
这种奢侈享受不是属于我们的
We crave a different kind of buzz
我们渴望一种别样的嗡嗡声
Let me be your ruler, you can call me queen bee
让我成为你的统治者 你可以叫我蜂王
And baby I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule
让我成为自己世界的统治者 自得自乐
Let me live that fantasy
实现自己的梦想
My friends and I we've cracked the code
我和伙伴们都明白了
We count our dollars on the train to the party
我们花费自己的美元坐火车前往聚会
And everyone who knows us knows that we're fine with this
认识我们的人都知道 但我们毫不在意
We didn't come from money
我们又不是从钱眼里钻出来的
But every song's like gold teeth
每首歌都庸俗如镶着黄金牙
Grey goose, trippin' in the bathroom
喝着伏特加 在自家打理形象
Blood stains, ball gowns, trashin' the hotel room
血腥 狂欢 在酒店搞破坏
We don't care, we're driving cadillacs in our dreams
对此我们习以为常 梦里的凯迪拉克毕竟遥远
But everybody's like cristal, maybach, diamonds on your time piece
但每个人都喜欢水晶 迈巴赫 手表镶满钻石
Jet planes, islands, tigers on a gold leash
乘着飞机去小岛 用金链子套老虎玩的生活
We don't care we aren't caught up in your love affair
我们不在乎这些 我对你的富贵梦廖无兴趣
And we'll never be royals
我们无法成为贵族
It don't run in our blood
没有那么高贵的血统
That kind of lux just ain't for us
这种奢侈享受不是属于我们的
We crave a different kind of buzz
我们渴望一种别样的嗡嗡声
Let me be your ruler, you can call me queen bee
让我成为你的统治者 你可以叫我蜂王
And baby I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule
让我成为自己世界的统治者 自得自乐
Let me live that fantasy
实现自己的梦想
Oooh ooooh ohhh
We're bigger than we ever dreamed
我们比梦想中更强大
And I'm in love with being queen
我喜欢上了当女王的感觉
Oooooh ooooh ohhhhh
life is game without a care
人生如梦不用担心
We aren't caught up in your love affair
我对你的富贵梦不感兴趣
And we'll never be royals
我们无法成为贵族
It don't run in our blood
我们没有那血统
That kind of lux just ain't for us
这种奢侈的享受不是属于我们的
We crave a different kind of buzz
我们需要不一样的声音
Let me be your ruler, you can call me queen bee
让我成为你的统治者 你可以叫我蜂王
And baby I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule I'll rule
从此我可以统制自己的世界 自得自乐
压制:随Feng
Let me live that fantasy
成就自己的梦想